welcome to another tutorial in this
欢迎使用本教程中的另一个教程
video we're going to be looking at the
我们将要观看的视频是
clone and the healing tools these are
克隆人和治愈工具
really powerful tools in and
和中真正强大的工具
they're not incredibly difficult to use
使用它们并不是非常困难
I'm gonna bring in some images to
我要带几张照片来
illustrate how these work we can either
说明这些功能的工作原理 我们可以
go to file open and I can find them on
打开文件 我可以在上面找到它们
my computer but I'm going to bring in
我的电脑 但我要把它带进来
three at once I'm going to just navigate
一次三个 我只需要导航
to the location which is on my desktop
到我桌面上的位置
I'm gonna left click and hold and select
我要左键点击并按住并选择
all three then left click and drag all
然后左键单击并拖动所有这三个
three of them just into this project
其中三个就进入了这个项目
area what that's gonna do is import all
这将会把所有的进口
three of these images and I can toggle
其中的三个图像 我可以切换
between which one I'm working on just
在我正在研究的哪一个之间
across this top selection bar up here
穿过这个最上面的选择栏
and so the first one I want to show is
所以我想要展示的第一个是
the clone tool so this is a picture just
克隆工具 所以这是一张图片
me standing in the snow and if I wanted
我站在雪地里 如果我想
to use the clone tool I can actually
要使用克隆工具 我实际上可以
clone multiple copies of myself is
克隆我自己的多个副本
standing here so the clone tool if we
站在这里 克隆人工具如果我们
hover over as the see is the shortcut
将鼠标悬停在See上 因为See是捷径
key to select it we found so just
键来选择它 我们找到了 所以只是
left-click on it and it has a lot of the
左键单击它 它会有很多
same options that we'd be familiar with
我们所熟悉的相同选项
other tools we can change the size of
我们可以更改的其他工具的大小
the brush the aspect ratio all these
画笔的纵横比所有这些
different things but what we really want
不同的东西 但我们真正想要的
to do I'm gonna size it to be about the
为此 我要把它的大小定为
size of my leg maybe that's about good
我的腿的大小可能还不错
enough right there and then to use this
足够了 就在那里 然后使用这个
tool now does it tell us here what we do
工具现在告诉我们我们在这里做什么了吗
is we hold down the ctrl key and then
就是我们按住Ctrl键然后
left-click one so I'm gonna hold down
左键单击一个 这样我将按住
the ctrl key and left-click at my foot
Ctrl键并在我的脚上单击鼠标左键
down here and that creates a dotted
在这里 这就产生了一个虚线
circle around my foot and now I can
绕着我的脚转 现在我可以
click anywhere else in the image and my
单击图像中的其他位置和我的
foot will start to be drawn right there
脚就会从那里开始被拉出来
I'm just left clicking and holding and
我只剩下点击和按住
it's just redrawing myself here I'll do
只是在这里重新画我自己 我会做的
ctrl Z because to make this more
Ctrl Z因为要让这个更多
realistic I'll keep that selection there
现实一点 我会把那个选择留在那里
and again to make that selection you
再一次让你做出这个选择
have to hold the ctrl key and then
必须按住Ctrl键 然后
left-click to choose this you're
左键单击以选择此选项
starting selection and then if I left
开始选择 然后如果我离开
click and hold right here for example I
点击并按住此处 例如I
can sort of put my foot right here and
可以把我的脚放在这里
just draw this very quickly a clone of
只需快速画出一个克隆
myself standing in the snow over here
我站在这里的雪地里
and the more time I take I can get it
我花的时间越多 我就能得到它
pretty looking pretty good and with
很漂亮 很漂亮 带着
notice over on the left hand side it's
注意在左手边是
showing me where I'm at on the source I
告诉我我在来源上的位置
guess the source part of the image and
猜测图像的源部分 并
then over here I'm just drying so I can
然后在这里 我只是在擦干 这样我就可以
sort of try to make sure I feel like a
试着让我感觉自己像个
feather on this tool right now which
现在这个工具上的羽毛
means that the edges are sort of a faded
意味着边缘是一种褪色
kind of fade out it's not like a hard
有点淡出 这不像是一场硬仗
drawn line anyway there we go that's not
不管怎么说 我们已经画好线了 这不是
too bad so I've got a clone of myself
太糟糕了 所以我有了一个克隆的自己
and as long as I keep holding down the
只要我一直按住
mouse the left mouse button I can come
鼠标左键我可以来
over and retouch up any of these areas
覆盖并润色这些区域中的任何一个
if I unclick the mouse button and then I
如果我取消单击鼠标按钮 然后我
try to click again it's going to start
试着再点击一次 它将开始
my source at that same point that I was
我的线人在同一时间 我是
at so I'll do ctrl Z to undo that that's
所以我会按Ctrl Z键来撤销这是
a very quick look at this and you notice
快速浏览一下 你就会注意到
if we zoom in here a little bit we can
如果我们把这里放大一点 我们可以
see it doesn't look exactly right the
看起来不太对劲
colors are off a little bit on this side
这一面的颜色有点不对劲
and that sort of fades into there's some
这种感觉渐渐淡出了一些
missing data there kind of but not too
那里的数据有点缺失 但也不是太多
bad for just illustrating how that clone
只是为了说明克隆人是如何
tool works a lot of times people will
工具在很多时候起作用 人们会
use this to do face swaps they'll select
用这个来做他们会选择的脸部交换
one person's face and then go over to
一个人的脸 然后走过去
the next area and an add in you know
下一个区域和一个插件 你知道的
replace just the face of a person I want
只替换我想要的人的脸
to show you another tool we can do so we
为了向您展示我们可以这样做的另一个工具 我们
could do the clone tool you could
可以做克隆工具 你可以
imagine erasing a part of an image we
想象一下 我们擦除了图像的一部分
could clone these rocks by holding down
可以通过按住这些岩石来克隆这些岩石
the ctrl key while we're still on the
Ctrl键 而我们还在
clone tool and then we could clone
克隆工具 然后我们就可以克隆
myself out and put some rocks here but
我自己在这里放了一些石头 但是
the problem is you get some
问题是你会得到一些
strange-looking things so if i zoom in
看起来很奇怪的东西 所以如果我放大
now it's kind of hard to see here but
现在在这里很难看到 但
we're really getting you can't really
我们真的得到了你不能真的
see all the detail in the rock and
看着岩石中的所有细节
especially with the trees it might look
尤其是有了这些树 它看起来
kind of strange the point that the trees
有点奇怪的是 这些树
overlap with each other it just doesn't
相互重叠 它只是不
look actually it looks pretty good but a
你看 实际上它看起来很不错 但是
better tool to use in this case is the
在这种情况下使用的更好的工具是
healing tool so I'll do ctrl Z the
修复工具 所以我将执行Ctrl Z The
healing tool is right next to the clone
修复工具就在克隆人旁边
tool has this band-aid icon on it all I
工具上有这个创可贴图标
want to mention your icons may look
想要提到你的图标可能看起来
different I can mention if the start of
不同的是 我可以提一下 如果
this I'm using a different version of
这是我使用的不同版本的
so if your icons look different it
所以如果你的图标看起来不一样
doesn't really matter different
不同并不重要
operating systems and different versions
操作系统和不同版本
display the icons differently
图标的显示方式不同
anyway I'll select this healing tool and
不管怎样 我会选择这个治疗工具
the healing tool works very similarly we
治疗工具的工作原理与我们
hold down the ctrl key to select an area
按住Ctrl键可选择一个区域
I'm gonna select this area right here
我要在这里选择这个区域
ctrl and then left click and that
Ctrl 然后左键单击
selects a pattern so this area is the
选择一种图案 使该区域成为
pattern on
图案打开
to use and now it behaves the same way
来使用 现在它的行为方式与
as the clone tool where I can left-click
作为克隆工具 我可以在其中左键单击
and then I can come and just sort of
然后我就可以过来 就像是
paint this out one thing I want to be
把这画出来 这是我想成为的一件事
careful of I should show this with a
小心 我应该用一个
clone tool if I go to the clone tool
如果我转到克隆工具 则使用克隆工具
it's a lot more pronounced with the
更明显的是
clone tool if ever I go too far so if I
克隆工具 如果我做得太过分 那么如果我
start erasing this but I go too far it's
开始抹去这一切 但我走得太远了
going to start cloning over my mouth
我要开始克隆我的嘴巴了
again even though it's not really there
再一次 即使它并不是真的在那里
it still remembers that old part of the
它仍然记得那个古老的部分
image so you have to be careful of where
图像 因此您必须注意位置
you set your reference point because if
您设置参考点是因为如果
you're not careful like the sky here if
如果你不像这里的天空那样小心
I start cloning down here and then move
我从这里开始克隆 然后搬家
up I'm gonna get the sky at a point I
我要在某一时刻飞向天空
don't really want it so it always just
并不是真的想要 所以它总是
stays relative to where you're at I
停留在相对于您所在位置的位置
don't I don't have a touch on the
我是不是一点都不懂
healing very much but the healing what
愈合得很好 但是治愈什么？
it really does is take a pattern and
它确实是采取了一种模式 并
then it uses a lot more processing power
然后它会使用更多的处理能力
so it's a lot slower but it sort of
所以它慢了很多 但它有点
heals and it sort of it sort of
治愈 这有点像是
eliminates that overlap so you don't get
消除了重叠 这样您就不会
that look of like part parts of the
看起来就像是
images are overlapped if there's a
如果存在以下情况 图像会重叠
pattern background or like grids or
图案背景或类似的网格或
something more complex and it's a solid
一些更复杂的东西 它是一个坚实的
color that's a good application to do
这是一个很好的应用程序
the healing but play with healing and
治疗 但玩弄治疗和治疗
clone and you'll notice a difference
克隆人 你会发现不同之处
another good example of something we
另一个很好的例子是我们
could do is these clouds if we made ours
如果我们制造了我们的云 我们能做的就是这些云
the size go down it's really easy to
尺码变小真的很容易
just get rid of a cloud make this bigger
只要除掉一片云 让这一切变得更大
so if we wanted to we choose this as our
因此 如果我们想要 我们选择这个作为我们的
reference point we maybe just go to
参照点 我们也许可以直接去
clone again for this one and then we can
再克隆一次 然后我们就可以
just kind of erase that cloud but we're
只是抹去了那片乌云 但我们正在
using this background but again if ever
使用这个背景 但如果曾经使用过的话
we get into our point if I start erasing
如果我开始删除 我们就进入正题了
this cloud but I go down it's going to
这朵云 但我走下去 它将会
redraw the cloud lower so just be aware
将云层重新画得更低 所以只需注意
of how that works if your point is too
如果你的观点太过
close to what you're working with you
接近你正在进行的工作
may have to select the point and then
可能需要选择该点 然后
you know make sure there's nothing in
你知道 要确保里面没有任何东西
the way like this mountain here or we
像这座山一样的路在这里还是我们
accidentally dry it up as you play with
你玩的时候不小心把它弄干了
that more you'll get more familiar one
越多 你就会越熟悉
more example I want to show you is this
我想给你们展示的更多例子是这个
picture here and this is one where the
照片在这里 这是一个在那里
healing tool makes a lot of sense this
治愈工具使这一点很有意义
is just an old image that has some lines
只是一张有一些线条的旧图像
if I hold down the shift and plus key on
如果我按住Shift键并按下+键
my keyboard I can zoom in here and we
我的键盘 我可以放大这里 我们
can see these lines where it's like a
我可以看到这些线条 它就像一个
fold and like some tears in the image
折叠并像图像中的一些泪水一样
well we can we could clone directly but
我们可以我们可以直接克隆但是
let me come
让我来吧
over here and take the size down a
在这里 把尺码降低一个
little bit and then we can grab our
一点点 然后我们就可以拿到我们的
healing tool and we'll select this area
修复工具 我们将选择此区域
right here hold down ctrl and left click
在这里按住ctrl并左键单击
so this is our target area our source
所以这就是我们的目标区域我们的源头
target and then as I left click here I
目标 然后当我单击此处时 我
can heal oh I forgot this one has an
可以治愈哦 我忘了这一个有一个
interesting issue with it this
这是一个有趣的问题
particular image down here at the bottom
下面这张底部的特定图像
it says healing does not operate on
它说治疗不会在
indexed layers that's because I'm using
索引层 这是因为我使用
a black and white image it doesn't have
它没有的黑白图像
a color doesn't have color channels so
颜色没有颜色通道 因此
if you run into this problem what you
如果你遇到这个问题 你会怎么做
need to do is go to image mode and go to
需要做的是进入图像模式并转到
RGB it's on indexed right now that
RGB现在已编入索引
doesn't happen often this happened to be
这并不经常发生 这恰好是
a scanned image and it's black and white
一张扫描过的黑白图像
and so for that reason that it's an
因此 出于这个原因 它是一种
indexed mode anyway now I can change
无论如何 索引模式现在可以更改
this so I can click here and I can
这样我就可以点击这里 我就可以
left-click and erase this tear line I
左键单击并删除这条撕裂线I
have an example of this several years
几年来我就有过这样的例子
ago in an older version of I'll
在旧版的《我会》中
show you that now this is repairing an
向你展示现在这是在修复一个
old image and kind of applying a little
古老的形象和某种程度的应用
bit of color adjustment but for the most
稍微调整一下颜色 但对大多数人来说
part using the healing tool to get rid
部分使用治疗工具来摆脱
of some of the tears and blemishes in
其中的一些撕裂和瑕疵
this old kind of battered image well
这种破旧的形象很好
hopefully you found that informative
希望你会觉得这很有用
guys go ahead and play with the clone
伙计们去玩克隆人吧
and healing tool there's a lot that you
和治疗工具 你有很多东西
can do between between getting rid of
可以在摆脱
things on an image and repairing parts
图像上的东西和修理部件
of images and even just cloning over
图像 甚至只是克隆
there's quite a bit you can do with just
你可以做的事情很多 只要
these without ever having to dive into
这些都不需要深入研究
selection which we're going to cover in
我们将在下面介绍的精选
future videos and some of these more
未来的视频和其中一些更多
advanced techniques go ahead and leave
先进的技术走在前面 然后离开
your question in the comments below if
您在下面的评论中的问题是
you have any and I look forward to
你有 我期待着
catching you in the next video
在下一个视频中看到你